[{"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What look", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What look", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I gave a look", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I know that look", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Thirt", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "We know the terrain", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Nope", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know. What do you think", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Devastating", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "And that would be good.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Because this is very good.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "That would be good too. The idea is combine the this and the that. But this cannot be disturbed", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It's bru", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Ready", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I think you're wrong", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Is this yours or the roommate's", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Hi, my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No, no. I have to be very careful here. I don't want to send the wrong message. Especially after the other night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, no. You can't get her anything better than me. Whatever I spend, you have to spend half", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Maybe I'll get her some jewelry", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What am I supposed to get, a bazooka", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I think I heard her say something about a bench", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't know, but she mentioned a bench", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Maybe you won't like it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You could not like it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Think where man's glory most begins and ends and say my glory was I had such a friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh my friend.", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You mean it's...  No this. No that. No this or that. Oh, boy. What do you want", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, if I call her, there's no joking around anymore. This is pretty much it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Deal.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Could be it", "qsentId": 36}]